This is the "Kubrick" template for Etomite. This template is based on "Kubrick" popularized by the weblog software WordPress. This template was ported to Etomite by Scotty Delicious. Please feel free to use this template as is on your website, or if you like, customize it to suite your needs.  If you make changes to this template, and you feel that it is useful, I do not expect a link back to my website (http://www.scottydelicious.com), but I do ask that you contribute your theme back to the forums at Etomite! Enjoy this template, and enjoy using Etomite!

By Scotty Delicious.
http://www.scottydelicious.com

------------------------------------------
installation
------------------------------------------

1.  	Copy the folder "kubricktheme" and all its contents (located in 	assets/templates/) to the folder assets/templates in your Etomite 	installation. You may need to create a "templates" folder in 	"assets" if it is not there already.

2.  	Open "kubrick.html" in a text editor, select all and copy, then 	create a new template in your Etomite manager and paste what you 	copied from "kubrick.html"

------------------------------------------

For questions or more information you can contact me at:
http://www.scottydelicious.com/mail.php